[
    {
        "question": "A feature/defect of a computer system that allows unauthorized access to data?",
        "correct_answer": "Back Door",
        "options": [
            "Back Door",
            "Trojan Horse",
            "Anti Virus",
            "Internet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the process of converting data to an unreadable form? (commonly used to protect sensitive information so that only authorized parties can view it)",
        "correct_answer": "Encryption",
        "options": [
            "Firewall",
            "Decryption",
            "Encryption",
            "Scrambling"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "An automated program that runs over the Internet?",
        "correct_answer": "Bot",
        "options": [
            "AI",
            "Bot",
            "Worm",
            "Broadband"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Software designed to protect against computer viruses?",
        "correct_answer": "Firewall",
        "options": [
            "Malware",
            "Defense",
            "White Hat Hacker",
            "Firewall"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Type of malware that records a victims keystrokes?",
        "correct_answer": "Keylogger",
        "options": [
            "Keylogger",
            "Keyboard",
            "Log File",
            "Worm"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What technique can help mitigate the impact of a ransomware attack?",
        "correct_answer": "Backup",
        "options": [
            "Restore",
            "Backup",
            "Antivirus",
            "Social Engineering"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recommended minimum password length?",
        "correct_answer": "8 characters",
        "options": [
            "None of the above",
            "12 characters",
            "8 characters",
            "6 characters"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does ransomware do?",
        "correct_answer": "Encrpts the victims disk",
        "options": [
            "Encrpts the victims disk",
            "Crashes the victims PC",
            "Gives you bitcoin",
            "Steals user credentials"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which password is strongest?",
        "correct_answer": "%R4diAnt99",
        "options": [
            "QWERTY",
            "abcdefg1234567",
            "dragon",
            "%R4diAnt99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT essential to cybersecurity?",
        "correct_answer": "Interoperability",
        "options": [
            "Confidentiality",
            "Integrity",
            "Availability",
            "Interoperability"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What should you do if your password is leaked of stolen?",
        "correct_answer": "Change my password",
        "options": [
            "Change my password",
            "Report it to the authorities",
            "Delete my account",
            "Wait a while to see what happens"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Your public key should be kept secret?",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "True",
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Asymmetric key encryption uses how many keys?",
        "correct_answer": "2 keys",
        "options": [
            "2 keys",
            "4 keys",
            "1 key",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is more secure?",
        "correct_answer": "HTTPS",
        "options": [
            "HTTPS",
            "HTTP",
            "HTTPS",
            "HTTP"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these attributes does NOT contribute towards a strong password?",
        "correct_answer": "Easy to remember",
        "options": [
            ">8 Characters",
            "Includes numbers and symbols",
            "Is not socially obtainable",
            "Easy to remember"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What word does the acronym DDoS NOT contain?",
        "correct_answer": "Daemon",
        "options": [
            "Distributed",
            "Denial",
            "Service",
            "Daemon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the first 'D' in DDoS stand for?",
        "correct_answer": "Distributed",
        "options": [
            "Distributed",
            "Denial",
            "Destruction",
            "Decryption"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is false, IDS/IPS stands for?",
        "correct_answer": "Instruction Protection Service",
        "options": [
            "Intrusion Detection System",
            "Intrusion Prevention System",
            "Instruction Protection Service",
            " "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hides the plaintext of a password?",
        "correct_answer": "Hashing",
        "options": [
            "Hashing",
            "Invisibility",
            "Password Manager",
            "Censorship"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of malware?",
        "correct_answer": "SQL Injection",
        "options": [
            "Keylogger",
            "Spyware",
            "Ransomware",
            "SQL Injection"
        ]
    }
]
